Hello friends, welcome to Share
Bana Inside channel.  Let's start today's market
update.  If I
talk about the market today, there has been neither much rise
, nor much bullish momentum nor
much fall because earlier the
market was up and then it bounced back.  Something like this is
going on right now.  You
can see here that if we talk about Nifty 50, there has been a
decline of around 8% and if we
talk about Bank Nifty, there has been a rise of 13%.  That
means there has been a close competition between the two
because banking stocks have
performed well and hence there is a boom again
in the market.  Here you can see that
first there was a decline and then there was a slight rise again.  If I
talk about some other indices today, you can see here that there has been only a
minor decline in Sussex.
Around 0.04%.  Talking about Nifty, there has been a
rise of around 0.23% in it.  And if we
talk about Bankex, it has seen a
rise of around 0.9%.  If I talk about some more
updates today, that is, stock
specific updates, then
news is coming from ICICI LBAT General Insurance
that they have received a tax
notice for
₹47.41
crore.  That means, a demand has been made by the GST department.
ICICI LBAT General Insurance has received a notice of ₹47 crores,
which is not a good thing for the company
because if such a huge demand has been received, then it will
probably have to pay it.  Because of this, if you
look at the stock price of the company, there has been a slight
decline [music].  Next, talking about
MSHO's IPO, it is being said that it has been
fully subscribed today.
Talking about total subscription, it
is fully subscribed.  If
we talk about the retail category, the IPO has been subscribed more than three times.  The
investors of the company have liked it very much,
hence it has received a very good response.
Now let us see
what will be the GMP when the market closes on 5th December
and what will be the subscription status of the company.
Next, if I talk about gold and
silver, then gold has again
touched its lifetime high.  Talking about Silver Jump, the
price of 1 kg is ₹184727.  This means that
silver has made a huge jump even today.   It has
reached its record time lifetime record high.  And if we talk about the price of gold, it is
running around ₹1,30,000.   That
means there has been a lot of rise in silver also.  The
value of our rupee is also decreasing
and the value of US dollar is increasing.
Because of this something big is going to happen in the market.
Now wait for a few days.  If
someone wants to make a big investment or
if this Russia-Ukraine matter settles down a bit
or there is a ceasefire between them, then there are
some chances of this market
doing well and the prices of gold and silver will
stop, then I will
not buy it until then because I think there is a
possibility of some big war in the coming time for
which I
can bring a dedicated video for you, if you
tell me in the comment then I will
definitely bring a dedicated video for it.
Next, if I talk about JSW Steel,
they have said that JF wants to buy
our 50% stake in JSW Kalinga. The
deal could be worth around Rs 15,750 crore. This is what
JSW Steel is saying right now, that is, their
subsidiary company is JSW Kalinga, so
JF wants to buy 50% stake in it and if we
look at the investors of the company, they did
not like it here, hence if we
look at the stop price of the company, there was a decline.
Next, if I talk about Vikram Solar,
they have said that our Arun Mittal
sir will now handle their energy storage
business, that is, he is going to
become their CEO.  Vikram Solar has a
wholly owned subsidiary company VSL, now
this is Arun Mittal sir.  He is going to be their CEO,
Chief Executive Officer.   For
now, the update was from Vikram Solar.
Next, if I talk about today's top gainers
and losers, you can see here that
Vodafone Idea has seen good growth.
Talking about Sonata software LED, there has been
good growth in it.  Talking about Triveni turbine, there has been
good growth in that too.
Talking about Bombay GMA Trading Corporation, there has been
good growth in it.
Talking about Sapphire Foods India, there was
good growth in that too.  Talking about the top two losers today,
Thyrocket Technologies has seen a
decline.  Sun Pharma Advanced Research has seen a
slight decline.  And if we talk about Indian Bank, there has been a
decline in it.  FS
India has also seen a decline.  And if we
talk about KNR Construction, there has been a
decline in it too.
Talking about some of the top global markets today, there was a
slight decline in Gift Nifty.  US 30 was
also moving rapidly.  Talking about US Tech 100, there was a
rise in it.  There has been a good rise in DJS
and there has also been a good rise in SNP 500.
Talking about the UK market, there was a
decline in it.  There was a
boom in the French market and there was also a boom in the Minor C and German
markets.  And if I
talk about the Japanese market, there was a good boom in it.
And if we talk about the Hanseng China market, there has been a huge
decline in it.
Talking about some economic indicators, 1
US dollar against IAR has
reached 90.70.  That means finally
our Indian Rupee has touched the figure of 90.  There has been a
huge decline
in our Indian Rupee which is
really not a good thing for India.  And if I talk about crude oil
prices, you
can see here that there has been a huge increase in both of them,
which is again
not a good thing for our India.  This is also a sign
of what is going to happen in the future.
If I see some such indicators then you can
go into the market right now or if
you want to go for the long term then you
can go.  But if you want to do something in the market in the short term, then
wait a bit
because something big is about to happen.  According to me,
I feel this way because the prices of gold and
silver are skyrocketing.  If we
talk about the prices of Band Crude Oil or crude oil, there has been a rise in them
too and the market is running quite volatile.  It is
neither going up nor going down.
So something big is about to happen.
I feel like that.  If you want me to make a
dedicated video on this, then
please let me know in the comments.
Talking about our update for today, this is all we have.
To watch such videos,
subscribe to our channel and don't
forget to turn on the bell icon.  Thanks for watching.